Soon, you’ll encounter something unexpected.
Conflict.
Arguments with a woman
or an old karmic debt.
You may face a major change.
The Tower card says…
that this change
will be like building a tower.
It won’t be easy.
Quite dangerous.
Before it’s complete,
it’ll take some time.
Trying to kill her like this.
How rotten are you?!
Help me.
Use the Krishna Kali spell on him!
I don’t want to die!
Please save Lord Gaew.
He’s not breathing anymore.
What?
What’s happening?
Am I dead?
You’re talking nonsense
like a lunatic.
Rich!
Help me.
I want to get out of here.
Rich?
Don’t you hear me?
Stop calling me so casually.
I’m Lord Muen Reung Ratchaphakdi.
What are you up to, Rich?
Will you stop being insolent, Gaew?
Rich.
What the hell?
Quit playing around.
Come with me to the police department.
What police department?
I’m confused.
Such insolence.
Arrest him, Muen Reung.
Yes.
This is ridiculous, Aunt.
Who is Gaew?
Everyone.
Listen to me.
My name…
is Great.
Great what?
Stop talking nonsense.
Take him away.
What are you doing?
Hey!
Let go of me.
Why are you arresting me?
I didn’t do anything wrong.
Let go!
My lord.
Juang’s bleeding won’t stop.
Let go. Let me go.
Let go. I’m a doctor!
Let go.
Gaew.
I think he’s gone mad.
He’s even claiming to be a doctor.
Juang.
Wake up.
My lady.
Please save my grandson.
Why are you all standing still?
Go get a doctor!
-Go!
-Yes, ma’am.
No need to go.
I’ll handle this.
Juang has arterial bleeding.
That’s why he’s bleeding this much.
We need to control the blood pressure.
What are you talking about?
So strange.
Right?
Acting like a doctor all of a sudden.
Let him try, Mother.
If you make a mistake,
I will never forgive you.
This is a man’s life,
not a toy.
I know a person’s life isn’t a toy.
Do you have any gauze?
I mean clean cloth.
Yes, we do.
Bring me clean cloth and water.
I’m going to clean his wound.
Yes, sir.
Excuse me.
Help me lift his legs.
Keep his legs up high.
It’ll slow the bleeding.
This way, he’ll lose less blood.
Even if you manage to save Juang,
he hurt this much because of you!
Reung.
Take him to the police department.
Punish him.
And take Yam, his wretched servant, with him!
Gaew.
I didn’t do anything wrong.
I’m not going anywhere.
If you didn’t do it,
then how did my boat sink?
How would I know?
I haven’t even seen a single boat.
Reung.
Why are you still standing there?
You have to come with me.
I didn’t do anything wrong.
Let go. Let go!
Reung.
Let me go.
It’s already late.
You can go get some rest.
That won't do, Dech.
They need to take him in for questioning.
Mother.
Tomorrow morning,
I’ll take Gaew to the police department myself.
-But I think…
-Jumpa!
That’s fine, Dech.
Then I’ll take my leave.
Gaew.
Come with me.
Come here.
Where are you taking me?
My lord.
I’m not Gaew. I’m Great!
I’m the reason you’re not arrested tonight.
So,
be good
and don’t cause any trouble.
Or I won’t be able to help you anymore.
Hey.
Are you not going to tell me
who you people are?
Where is this place?
And what do you want?
You talk strangely.
You.
Aren’t you going to tell me who you are?
Don’t call me “Khun.”
I’m merely a "Muen."
What’s a "Muen"?
(‘Khun’ means ‘You’, but it’s also a high lord title.)
(Muen ranks lower than Khun.)
You're acting cool, huh?
('Thumb Song' means 'acting cool', but 'Song' is also a royal prefix.)
“Song”?
What do you mean?
Song is a royal prefix.
If other people overhears that,
your head will roll.
Jeez.
Why so fierce.
Fierce?
I’m not fierce.
This isn’t fierce?
You’re frowning and scowling.
Are you criticizing me?
No. I’m just telling the truth.
Then,
I’ll call you…
P’Muen.
Okay?
What does “okay” mean?
Okay means agreed.
Such a strange word.
You make no sense.
It’s as if you’re possessed.
Yam.
Yes, sir.
Keep a close eye on your master.
Oh, right.
What’s your name?
Me?
Yes.
There’s only the two of us here.
My lord.
You even forget my name?
My name is Yam.
Yam.
What era are we in right now?
Era?
What’s an era?
I mean the reign.
Which reign is this?
You mean who's our ruler?
Yeah, who is it?
Our ruler is Khun Luang Narai, sir.
Khun Luang Narai?
Khun Luang Narai.
King Narai?
Huh?
Did I really travel back more than 300 years?
My lord. My lord.
My lord.
I can’t figure out
why the Krishna Kali spell…
affected Gaew like this.
I think
we may have been wrong from the start.
Maybe Gaew isn’t the culprit.
How could it not be him?
But Gaew is completely unharmed.
He just seems insane, right?
The fact that Gaew is still alive
means that he
is innocent.
The Krishna Kali spell
cannot harm an innocent person.
But what surprises me is…
He’s not the same Gaew as before.
Isn’t that right?
Finally, it's morning.
What a crazy dream.
Whoa!
Am I still dreaming?
But if this is real,
then how did I get here?
Where’s the mirror?
What?
Whose body is this?
My lord.
You even forgot who you are.
If I could travel back in time,
then I must be able to go back.
But how do I go back?
I don’t even know how I got here.
Grandma’s probably stressed out
that her blood pressure has risen.
Hey.
Where’s the bathroom?
Bathroom?
What’s a bathroom?
The place where you pee and poop.
Right here.
The chamber pot.
You expect me to pee in it?
This is insane.
I need to take a dump.
This way, sir.
Lord Gaew.
Where?
Stop!
I knew you’d try to run away.
Nonsense. I’m not running away.
Let’s go.
Stop! Where are you going?
To the toilet.
The toilet?
What’s a toilet, and what do you do there?
To take a dump.
Come on, Yam.
Hey, Gaew.
Gaew will escape through the vej.
(Vej is an ancient Thai toilet.)
This way, sir.
Here is the vej.
"Vej"?
As in wet?
It’s not wet, sir.
People actually poop here?
Yes, we poop here.
Hmm.
Luxurious.
Luxurious?
What does that mean?
He really forgot everything.
He doesn’t even recognize a vej.
Goodness.
I feel much better.
P’Yam.
I’m done.
Where’s the toilet paper?
Toilet paper?
What’s that?
You know,
paper for wiping your butt.
Well…
it's that bamboo tube over there.
This one?
Isn't it a fortune stick?
That’s not a fortune stick.
It’s a butt wiping stick.
A butt wiping stick?
Wouldn’t it tear your butt apart?
Hey.
Why are you following me?
Well…
I thought you’d run away.
I’m not running away.
I’m here to poop.
P'Yam, I need to wash up.
This way, sir.
Hey!
Why are you pulling my clothes?
Can’t bear it?
I haven’t washed my butt.
-Come on, P’Yam.
-This way, sir.
He’s strange.
More like insane.
P’Yam.
What’s this stick for?
It’s a toothbrush stick.
We use it with ash and salt.
What about...
this round thing?
Soapberry, sir.
For scrubbing your body.
Soapberry?
Ah!
That Muen acting cool.
Who is he?
Acting cool?
Lord Muen’s name is Dech.
You really forgot everything.
Come on, P’Yam.
People forget things.
So,
who is Gaew?
Huh?
You’re Gaew.
Have you really lost your memory?
I’m getting worried.
Okay.
I’m Gaew.
Then,
where are my parents?
Your parents passed away.
Your father was Lord Ramnarong.
Your mother was Pudjeeb,
a relative of Lady Jumpa,
who's Lord Muen’s mother.
My head hurts.
Nice build.
That poser.
What did you say?
I said you’re handsome.
I’m giving you a like.
What’s a like?
Nothing.
It’s nothing.
Pin, bring the clothes.
Hurry up and get dressed.
You’re coming to the police department with me.
What’s that sound?
My stomach is growling.
I’m getting hungry.
I’ll go get your clothes first.
All done.
Now that’s more like it.
I look more like Great now.
What’s up, P’Yam?
Hurry up. I’m hungry.
Yes, sir.
Don’t run, my lord
Wow.
The table’s loaded.
Where are your manners?
Sorry.
Come.
Have breakfast with us.
Thank you. I’m starving.
Hey, Pin!
Yes?
Why aren't you moving?
Go get Gaew a plate!
Yes, sir.
That’s right.
Alright.
You may eat now.
Let's eat.
So people here still eat with their hands?
If not with your hands, then what?
Our feet?
Prik!
Auntie.
Please let me finish first.
I was going to say that
eating with your hands is actually good.
It stimulates digestion
through sensing the food’s temperature.
It helps improve mindfulness while eating
and strengthens the connection
between us and our food.
And it helps improve blood circulation.
There he goes again.
Good grief.
What a weirdo.
It’s not strange, Jumpa.
It’s called Ayurveda.
You’re eating like a baby.
Making such a mess.
At this rate, Yam might have to feed you.
Come on.
Argh!
I’ll excuse myself.
I can’t stand him.
Prik, let’s go back to my room.
Yes, my lady.
Your water, sir.
It’s rainwater.
So refreshing.
I’ve never had anything like this.
I usually only drink mineral water.
Huh?
Mineral water?
Yes.
Go get ready.
You have to come to the police department with me.
Muen Reung sent word that Lord Gaew
doesn’t need to go to the police department.
Huh?
Don’t “huh”.
Go tell your master.
Yeah, yeah.
Pin.
Yes, sir.
P’Yam.
Let me ask you something.
Why does P’Muen hate me so much?
You and Lord Muen never got along.
Every time you meet, you end up arguing.
Because Lord Muen is sharp
more intelligent,
and he's a skilled swordsman.
So you always lose to him.
I…
I’m sorry. I deserve to die.
Please beat me all you want,
but please don’t send me to the slave quarters.
Hey.
I'm not angry.
Go on.
What else did I do to make him hate me?
Give me the worst one.
The worst one?
Yes.
You ordered me to sink his boat.
But that day, Lady Jumpa was on the boat.
Dech.
Reung.
Have they found Noi’s body?
She’s not dead.
A villager rescued her.
She’s at Phanan Choeng temple now.
But she’s still not making any sense.
Maybe because she was underwater for too long.
In that case, Gaew…
He won’t have to be punished for causing someone’s death.
What happened at your house last night, Dech?
Why do I feel like Gaew has changed?
I’m not sure yet.
Did he really try to kill someone?
That’s a grave sin.
Oh, Gaew.
I’ll go refill the tea first.
I can’t stay here.
If I stay any longer,
I’ll be dead for sure.
But how do I get back?
If lightning...
brought me here,
then it could send me back as well.
Come on, strike me!
Come at me.
Gaew.
What are you doing, Gaew?
Lord Muen.
What are you doing?
What spirit possessed you
to do something like this?
I’m not possessed.
And I’m not insane.
I’m perfectly sane.
Don’t lie to me.
Why are you doing this?
Will you even believe me?
Just tell me.
I want lightning to strike me,
so I can go back to where I came from.
Huh?
You’ve lost your mind.
Your way of thinking is so strange.
Don’t ever do this again.
It’s an order.
Go back inside!
Please head back too.
You’ll catch a cold.
Will you even believe me?
Just tell me.
I want lightning to strike me,
so I can go back to where I came from.
Lord Muen.
You look troubled.
What’s wrong?
It’s Gaew.
Something isn’t right.
Did Lord Gaew do something?
Ever since he woke up, he’s been different.
Nothing he says makes sense.
And he seems
to remember nothing at all.
Like a different person.
I totally agree.
Maybe it’s because of the Krishna Kali spell.
That spell is powerful.
Even if it doesn’t kill him, it could drive him insane.
I’m also not sure
what exactly happened to Gaew.
I only hope that
this change
is for the better.
That’s Lord Gaew.
Who is that, P’Yam?
That’s Lord Saen.
Last time,
your fighting rooster beat every one of his.
So he’s very furious.
Let’s go, P’Yam.
Where are you going?
Nowhere. Nothing.
Hey!
My lord!
Why’d you kick me?
Last time, your rooster beat all of mine.
This time, I won’t let you go.
Where’s your rooster?
Let my Khun Thong stomp it into the ground.
I don’t have a rooster.
And isn’t Khun Thong a bird species?
Don’t toy with me.
I have to go.
Don’t come any closer.
I’m serious.
Get him!
My lord.
Lord Muen.
Lord Gaew…
This Gaew doesn’t seem like the old Gaew.
If he’s not Lord Gaew, then who is he?
He’s familiar, but not the same.
He’s different , but not that different.
Isn’t that right, Pin?
I’m confused.
It’s been a long time, P’Jumpi.
What brings you all the way here today?
Gaew beat Saen up in the middle of the market.
Good heavens!
How could this happen?
Is Saen alright?
I don’t care how it happened.
You need to deal with him for me.
Don't let him see the light of day again.
Saen is your grandson.
Gaew is only a distant relative.
If you keep him in this house,
one day he might betray you.
At this rate,
Gaew might spit in the water
that you drink every day.
For heaven’s sake, Prik!
I’m about to faint.
Throw him out immediately.
Kick him out of the capital.
Make him suffer for all eternity!
We need to talk.
You assaulted Saen, my sister’s son.
And brought shame upon my ancestors
in front of the whole market.
I didn’t mean to hurt anyone.
You didn’t mean to?
You nearly beat him to death!
If he had meant to,
wouldn’t he have dug up your ancestors’ bones
and trampled on them?
Prik!
I didn’t start the fight.
He came after me first.
He's just all talk.
You all should…
Uh…
Auntie, you should know your nephew well.
And I know you well too, Gaew.
Calm down, Jumpa.
We should hear both sides of the story.
Why don’t we bring Saen and Jumpi here to talk?
Dech, come on.
Deal with him for me.
If things happened the way Mother and Aunt said,
then you deserve punishment.
But I want to hear it from you first.
What happened?
I admit
that Saen and I got into a fight.
But what I did,
was for self defense.
I didn’t mean to.
I’m sorry.
I know...
that in the past,
Gaew did many bad things to you guys.
But today,
can I have a chance to become a better person?
There’s no greater kindness
than forgiveness
and a second chance.
That sounds nice coming from him.
Prik!
Yes, ma’am.
If in the past,
I’ve wronged anyone,
whether intentionally
or unintentionally,
I’m sorry.
I really am.
I ask for your forgiveness.
From today on,
I’m a new Gaew.
Juang.
Yes, sir.
Go prepare a boat.
Where are you going?
I’m going to negotiate with Jumpi.
Do you want me to go with you?
No.
Gaew.
Come with me.
Let me handle this for you.
I think Lord Gaew must be possessed,
so he changed drastically.
I think so too, Aunt Prik.
Before, if someone got on his nerves,
he’d kick them, and curse them out like dogs.
But just now,
he knelt down and apologized in tears.
You’re exaggerating.
Did you even see his tears?
I just feel it.
Lord Muen…
also think that Lord Gaew isn’t the same Gaew.
He must be possessed.
Which spirit is this?
I really want to know.
Lord Gaew changed
after recovering from the spell.
All my life,
I’ve only ever heard
that the Krishna Kali spell punishes evil people.
I’ve never heard
it could turn a bad person into a good one.
The servants are gossiping about you.
Let them talk.
They’re doing that because they hate me.
The old Gaew.
What do you mean?
The old Gaew?
It’s nothing.
Go get some sleep.
I’m sleepy.
Yes, sir.
P’Yam.
Yes?
Do you have a mosquito net?
Mosquito nets are only for the masters.
A servant like me doesn't have one.
Aren’t you afraid of getting dengue fever or malaria?
Malaria?
I forgot.
People here don’t know about it yet.
I mean
jungle fever or shaking fever.
Oh.
I see.
You should go to sleep.
Yes, sir.
I brought mosquito nets, pillows, and blankets for you guys.
So you won’t get bitten by mosquitoes.
Everyone can have it.
Your sleeping quarters must be kept clean.
Don’t let dust or water collect anywhere.
So mosquitoes can’t lay eggs and make you sick.
Close the water jars too.
These mosquitoes can kill us.
Don’t leave any standing water around.
If anyone gets bitten and has a high fever,
tell me immediately.
Don’t ignore it.
Lord Gaew handed out mosquito nets,
pillows, and blankets to the servants.
He also told us
to clean our sleeping quarters.
Wasn’t he implying that
P’Hora and I didn’t take good care of the servants?
At this rate, this house will end up becoming his.
He’s being generous.
Why would you hate it?
Good and evil
can’t be forced on
or taken away by others.
Maybe
Gaew is just trying to be a better person.
This house
will always be ours.
Our servants
No one can take them away.
He’s helping us take care of the servants.
Isn’t that great?
Let him do that.
Ahem.
This is just a common chickenpox.
Yam.
Bring me some herbs.
I want turmeric, betel leaves, and coriander roots.
Yes, sir.
I’ll make an ointment for you.
Don’t worry, guys.
This isn’t a serious illness.
You’ll recover soon.
He has no respect for you, my lady.
Look at him.
And you.
You should try to lose some weight.
He's talking to you.
No, you.
Both of you.
Be careful of fatty liver disease.
As you get older, your arteries can clog.
Which causes a heart attack.
But don’t worry.
If you pay attention to your diet…
Just you wait, Gaew.
I won’t let this slide.
You’re just in time, Dech.
What’s going on?
Bua.
Why are you crying?
This servant…
is pregnant with Gaew’s child.
Prik.
Go bring Gaew to me.
Yes.
You.
You go.
Pregnant?
With my child?
I’ve never…
Enough with the excuses.
You got her pregnant.
You have to take responsibility.
Father. Mother.
I’m back.
P’Sri.
Sri, you’re back.
Oh?
Did Gaew cause trouble again?
This is unripe durian fried until crispy.
What is this?
Is this really fried durian?
How did I live without it before?
Stay here.
P’Muen?
I think you’re…
cuter now?
My lord!
Gaew!
My lord, lord Muen went underwater.